Guide to The Billie Jean King Collection 1901-2019 (bulk, 1940-2019) MS 3147
New-York Historical Society
- Series VIII. Photographs, 1935-2020; 10 Linear feet in 6.5 record cartons, 2 flat boxes, and oversize folders
  - Subseries VIII.B. Career, 1955-2005; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Subseries VIII.B contains photographs taken throughout BJK's career as a tennis player, tennis coach, and broadcaster. The majority of photos are tennis match shots, including court play and BJK with awards. Notable files include a group of Wimbledon photos and photos from the Battle of the Sexes match against Bobby Riggs. Photos date from 1955-2005.
    - Early tennis career (2 folders), 1955-1960 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 22-23)
      Photos of BJK playing tennis, with trophies, and with other players during her Juniors tennis career.
    - Early tennis career [oversized], circa 1955-1965 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 3)
    - Early tennis career - Beverly Hills Tennis Club [oversized], 1957 December 27 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 2)
      Includes two mounted photos of BJK at the Beverly Hills Tennis Club with trophy.
    - Tennis career (3 folders), 1961-1980 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 24-26)
      Contains tennis match photos of BJK throughout her singles and doubles career, including play with Martina Navratilova and Chris Evert, as well as press photos and photos with trophies.
    - Wimbledon, The Championships (2 folders), 1961-1975 (Offsite-box 45, Folder 27-28)
      Contains photos of BJK competing at Wimbledon, holding the Rosewater Dish trophy, and with doubles partners, as well as press photos from Wimbledon.
    - Tennis career [oversized], 1970s (Offsite-box 57, Folder 4)
      Contains 10 x 15 inch photos of BJK with Wimbledon trophy in 1975 and BJK with Battle of the Sexes trophy.
    - Battle of the Sexes match against Bobby Riggs (2 folders), 1973 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 1-2)
    - Tennis career [oversized], 1974 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 3)
      Contains large format mounted photograph of BJK playing in Virginia Slims of Philadelphia match taken by Edward Fernberger.
    - Federation Cup, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 3)
    - Federation Cup [oversized], 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 4)
      One photo mounted on foam board of BJK and Federation Cup team.
    - NBC Sports, circa 1990s (Offsite-box 46, Folder 4)
    - HBO, circa 1990s-2000s (Offsite-box 46, Folder 5)
    - Fed Cup, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 6)
      Contains photos of the 1995-1996 United States Fed Cup team coached by BJK.
    - Fed Cup [oversized], 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 5)
    - Fed Cup [oversized], 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 4)
      One photo of BJK mounted on foam board.
    - Headshots (4 folders), 1960-2005 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 7-10)
    - BJK portrait removed from frame, circa 1960s-1970s (Offsite-box 64, Folder 4)
    - Headshots [oversized], 2000s (Offsite-box 57, Folder 6)
    - BJK contact sheets and negatives, circa 1960s-1990s (Offsite-box 46, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VIII.C. TeamTennis, 1974-2006; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Subseries VIII.C contains photographs from the TeamTennis, Domino's Pizza TeamTennis, and World TeamTennis leagues. Subjects of photos include team rosters, match shots, community recreation league events, and the annual WTT Smash Hits benefit. A portion of this group of photos was originally organized in binders, and this arrangement has been maintained with a note in the folder title indicating so. Photos date from 1974 to 2006.
    Files are arranged in chronological order.
    - BJK Philadelphia Freedoms, 1974 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 12)
    - WTT, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 13)
    - WTT [oversized], 1976-1990s (Offsite-box 57, Folder 7)
    - TeamTennis, circa 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 14)
    - WTT Chicago Fyre [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1983 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 15-16)
    - TeamTennis, circa 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 17)
    - TeamTennis teams, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 18)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis, 1985 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 19)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis teams, 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 20)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis (7 folders), circa 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 21-27)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis negatives, circa 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 46, Folder 28)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis - BJK, circa 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 1)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis and TeamTennis Rec League negatives (3 folders), circa 1985-1995 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 2-4)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis Championship Award ceremony, 1989 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 5)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis (6 folders), 1990 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 6-11)
    - TeamTennis Ultra Slim Fast (2 folders), 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 12-13)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis Chicago Tennis Fest, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 14)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis and TeamTennis [oversized], circa 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 5)
      Contains photo of BJK and others in Domino's Pizza TeamTennis apparel mounted on foam board and photo of the 1991 TeamTennis Champions Atlanta Thunder team mounted on board and signed by the team.
    - TeamTennis, circa 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 15)
    - TeamTennis Rec Day Atlanta, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 16)
    - TeamTennis Rec Day Charlotte, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 17)
    - TeamTennis Rec Day Hershey PA, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 18)
    - TeamTennis Rec Day Minneapolis, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 19)
    - TeamTennis Rec Day New Jersey, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 20)
    - TeamTennis Rec Day New York, 1991 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 21)
    - WTT teams, 1991-1995 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 22)
    - WTT, circa 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 23)
    - WTT party, 1992 September (Offsite-box 47, Folder 24)
    - San Diego after school tennis program, 1992 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 25)
    - WTT Rec Day Chicago/Wilmette, 1992 March 7 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 26)
    - WTT Rec Day Tampa, 1992 May 2 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 27)
    - WTT Rec Day Central Park, 1992 August 20 (Offsite-box 47, Folder 28)
    - WTT team photos, 1993 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 1)
    - WTT Rec Day Boston, 1993 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 2)
    - TeamTennis Regional Clinic Washington D.C., 1993 April 17 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 3)
    - WTT Smash Hits - Carol Newsom (2 folders), 1994 July 26 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - WTT school and community programs, 1994 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 6)
    - WTT Smash Hits Chicago, IL [disassembled binder], 1995 September 13 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 7)
    - WTT Smash Hits Houston, TX [disassembled binder] (4 folders), 1996 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 8-11)
    - WTT Smash Hits Orlando, FL [disassembled binder], 1997 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 12)
    - WTT Smash Hits Chicago, IL [disassembled binder], 1998 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 13)
    - WTT Smash Hits [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 14-15)
    - WTT Smash Hits (3 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 16-18)
    - WTT Smash Hits [disassembled binder], 2000 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 19)
    - WTT Smash Hits auction items, circa 2000 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 20)
    - WTT Smash Hits BJK and Elton John, circa 2000s (Offsite-box 48, Folder 21)
    - WTT Smash Hits, circa 2000s (Offsite-box 48, Folder 22)
    - WTT, 2002 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 23)
    - WTT Smash Hits Boston, MA [disassembled binder], 2003 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 24)
    - WTT Smash Hits [disassembled binder], 2004 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 25)
    - WTT Smash Hits [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2005 (Offsite-box 48, Folder 26-27)
    - WTT semifinals [disassembled binder], 2005 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 1)
    - WTT Judith Arnold, 2006 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 2)
  - Subseries VIII.D. Events, 1960-2020; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Subseries VIII.D includes photographs from various events attended by BJK, including fundraising events, sporting events, awards presentations, and television appearances. Notable events include BJK's induction into the International Tennis Hall of Fame, induction into the National Women's Hall of Fame, and renaming ceremony for the USTA BJK National Tennis Center. Photos date from 1960 to 2020.
    Photographs are arranged chronologically, with general event folders containing events with one or a few photos followed by files for individual events.
    - Events (5 folders), 1980s-2000s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 3-7)
      Contains event photo files grouped in chronological order by proximate dating. Most photos do not have a date specified. Many events have a single photo. Event types include social gatherings, tennis matches, reunions, fundraising events, and award presentations.
    - Events [oversized], 1984-2018 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 8)
      Includes photo board from the 1984 Virginia Slims Championships and photo from the 2018 Golden Globe Awards.
    - Events [oversized] (2 folders), 1997-2000s (Offsite-box 58, Folder 6-7)
      Contains photo of notable attendees of the US Open Singles Championships August 25, 1997, photo of the Champions Parade group at Wimbledon 2000, mounted photo of BJK parachuting with the U.S. Army Parachute Team Golden Knights, including signatures of Team members, and photo of CSULA student athletes with autographs.
    - Events [oversized], circa 2000s (Offsite-box 60, Folder 4)
      Contains group photo of unidentified event. BJK and Elton John at center of group. Elton John signed photo.
    - Event photos removed from frames, 1980s-2000s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 8)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research, 1994 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 9)
    - Awards (2 folders), 1960s-2000s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 10-11)
      Contains photos of BJK awards, including tennis tournament trophies, honorary degrees, and various award presenations and ceremonies.
    - Adventures in Movement, circa 1990s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 12)
    - Art Seitz photography, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 13)
    - Arthur Ashe Safe Passage Foundation Victory Dinner, 1995 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 14)
    - BNP Paribas, 2009 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 15)
    - Cal State Commencement, 1997 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 16)
    - Cal State Commencement [oversized], 1997 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 9)
    - Credit Suisse First Boston, 2005 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 17)
    - Davis Cup Spain vs USA, 2008 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 18)
    - HISTORYTalks, 2020 February 29 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 14)
    - Homecoming with Rick Reilly, 2010 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 19)
    - Indianapolis starter flag, 2008 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 20)
    - International Tennis Hall of Fame Celebrating 50 Years, 2004 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 4)
    - International Tennis Hall of Fame Eugene Scott Award honoring Chris Evert, 2012 August (Offsite-box 49, Folder 21)
    - International Tennis Hall of Fame induction, 1987 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 22)
    - March for Our Lives, 2018 March 18 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 23)
    - National Women's Hall of Fame, 1990 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 24)
    - National Women's Law Center, 2004 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 25)
    - Pat Parsons photocopies, circa 2000s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 26)
    - Television appearances, 1970s-2000s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 27)
      Contains photos from BJK's appearance on various television programs, including the Mike Douglas Show, The Sonny & Cher Comedy Hour, The Odd Couple, Dinah! with Dinah Shore, Game Time with Boomer Esiason, The Oprah Winfrey Show, and the Tavis Smiley Show, as well as BJK with Holly Hunter on the set of the film "When Billie Beat Bobby."
    - Teneo, 2012 October 17 (Offsite-box 64, Folder 15)
      Contains photo of BJK, Ilana Kloss, Bill Clinton, and George W. Bush at Teneo event.
    - USTA renaming ceremony, 2006 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Slims Legends tour, 1990s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 29)
    - Virginia Slims Championship Series, 1980s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 30)
    - White House, 1975-1999 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 31)
      Contains photos of BJK at the White House, including BJK with President Ford and Arthur Ashe, BJK with President Reagan, and event photos from HBO documentary screening at White House with President Clinton.
    - Wimbledon, 2005-2019 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 32)
    - Wimbledon Royal Box, 2014-2019 (Offsite-box 13, Box 13C)
      Contains photos from The Championships, Wimbledon of the Royal Box spectators, each including a seating chart naming guests of the Box.
    - Wimbledon / WTA gathering, circa 1990s (Offsite-box 49, Folder 33)
    - womenSports, 1974-1980 (Offsite-box 49, Folder 34)
    - Women's Sports Foundation [oversized], 1998-2006 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 10)
      Includes formal group photo from the Annual Salute to Women in Sports Award Dinner 1998, 1999, and 2000 and photo board from The Billies 2006.
    - Women's Sports Foundation [oversized], circa 2000 (Offsite-box 60, Folder 4)
      Various photos from the WSF Annual Salute to Women in Sports event featuring BJK displayed together on board with caption reading "To Our T.E.A.M. Leader The Women's Sports Foundation Staff."
    - Women's Sports Foundation (1 of 4 folders), 2000s (Offsite-box 49, Box 35)
    - Women's Sports Foundation (3 of 4 folders), 2000s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 1-3)
    - Women's Sports Foundation Advanta event, 2005 July 19 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 4)
    - WTA tour, 2005 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 5)
  - Subseries VIII.E. People, 1960-2017; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Subseries VIII.E includes photograph files of particular people or groups of people, including individual shots, the identified person with BJK, and event photos of particular people and groups of people. Notable individuals include Hillary Clinton, Elton John, BJK's life partner Ilana Kloss, Barack Obama, and the Original 9. The subseries also includes a file of photos autographed and given to BJK by the subject. Photos date from 1960 to 2017.
    Arranged alphabetically followed by files of photographs signed by subject.
    - Casals, Rosemary "Rosie", 1960s-1990s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 6)
      Contains photos of Rosie Casals, tennis player and BJK's doubles partner, including event photos and match shots with BJK.
    - Clinton, Hillary, 1999-2017 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 7)
    - Congress, 1984-2012 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 8)
      Contains photos of BJK with members of Congress at various events, including BJK and Geraldine Ferraro, BJK and Senator Ted Kennedy, and BJK with Senator Birch Bayh, author of the Title IX law.
    - Friends (2 folders), 1970s-2000s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 9-10)
      Contains photos of BJK and friends. Folder was present in the collection before processing and order and folder title were maintained.
    - John, Elton (3 folders), 1970s-2000s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 11-13)
      Contains photos of BJK and Elton John, many from TeamTennis events and Elton John AIDS Foundation events.
    - John, Elton and BJK [oversized], 1980s (Offsite-box 58, Folder 8)
      Contains three copies, one mounted on board, of BJK and Elton John portrait.
    - King, Larry, 1964-1977 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 14)
    - Kloss, Ilana (3 folders), circa 1970s-2000s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 15-17)
      Contains photos of Ilana Kloss, BJK's life partner. Photos include Ilana Kloss playing throughout her tennis career, at events, and with BJK.
    - Kloss, Ilana [oversized], 1980s (Offsite-box 57, Folder 11)
    - Navratilova, Martina, circa 1970s-2000s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 18)
    - Obama, Barack, 2009-2016 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 19)
      Contains photos of BJK and President Barack Obama at White House, including BJK receiving the Presidential Medal of Freedom in 2009.
    - Obama, Barack [oversized], 2009 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 12)
      Includes two 10 x 15 inch photos of BJK receiving the Presidential Medal of Freedom from Barack Obama.
    - Obama, Barack [oversized], 2009 (Offsite-box 58, Folder 9)
      Contains 16 x 20 inch photo of BJK and Barack Obama at the ceremony for the Presidential Medal of Freedom award.
    - Obama, Michelle, 2009-2011 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 20)
    - Original 9, 1970-2012 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 21)
      Contains photos of the Original 9 and tennis promoter Gladys Helman posing with their original dollar bills and together over time at various reunions and commemorative events.
    - Sotomayor, Justice Sonia, circa 2010 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 22)
      Contains photo of Justice Sonia Sotomayor with BJK and Ilana Kloss.
    - Steinem, Gloria and Dr. Sally Ride, 1983 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 23)
      Contains photo of BJK with Gloria Steinem and Dr. Sally Ride.
    - Virginia Slims Legends, 1990s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 24)
      Contains headshots of tennis players in the Virgina Slims Legends tour.
    - Women's Sports Legends (3 folders), circa 1995 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 25-27)
      Includes photo files of athletes of the Women's Sports Legends business.
    - Signed photos (2 folders), 1960s-2000s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 28-29)
      Contains photos signed by subjects and many dedicated to BJK. Photos and signatures include Althea Gibson, Elton John, the World TeamTennis New York Apples team, Venus and Serena Williams, and Virginia Slims Legends players. Also includes BJK photo signed to Ilana Kloss.
    - Signed photos [oversized], 2005 (Offsite-box 57, Folder 13)
      Contains formal photo of MGM actors taken in 1943 with personalized note and autograph to BJK from Esther Williams.
  - Subseries VIII.F. Slides, 1959-1997; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Subseries VIII.F includes slides, the majority of which capture TeamTennis matches and events. All slides in the collection are included in this subseries, excepting slides originally included in TeamTennis binders, which have been kept in Subseries VIII.C. Slides date from 1959 to 1997.
    - BJK court shots, 1959-1983 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 30)
    - Personal, 1973-1997 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 31)
      Contains slides of BJK and friends and family.
    - World TeamTennis, circa 1974-1980 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 32)
    - Avis Challenge Cup Hawaii, 1976 (Offsite-box 50, Folder 33)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis, 1980s (Offsite-box 50, Folder 34)
    - TeamTennis Chicago Fyre, circa 1983 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1988 Pro and Rec and 1987 Hall of Fame [disassembled binder] (2 folders) (Offsite-box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - TeamTennis Honolulu, circa 1985-1990 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 4)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis, 1986 July (Offsite-box 51, Folder 5)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis, 1987 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 6)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis Midtown Rec Day, 1987 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 7)
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis Rec Days, 1987 June (Offsite-box 51, Folder 8)
    - World TeamTennis, 1990 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 9)
    - BJK headshots, circa 1997 (Offsite-box 51, Folder 10)
- Series IX. (RESTRICTED) Audiovisual and digital formats, 1973-2018; 1 Linear feet
  Series IX includes audiovisual and digital media collected by BJK. Formats of material include audiocassettes, videocassettes, a betacam tape, mini-DVs, VHS tapes, CDs, DVDs, and a USB flash drive. Content of media includes audio recordings of TeamTennis stakeholder meetings and ads, audio and video footage of various events and BJK interviews, commercially-released DVD films, and CDs gifted to BJK by Elton John.
  Arranged in four subseries:
  Subseries IX.A. Audiocassettes
  Subseries IX.B. Videocassettes
  Subseries IX.C. Optical disks [CDs and DVDs]
  Subseries IX.D. USB flash drives
  This series is currently restricted from use. The videotapes and audiotapes are restricted because of their fragility and because N-YHS has no equipment on which to play them. The digital media is restricted from access in order to ensure that the digital files are not accidentally corrupted. N-YHS will be developing procedures to properly handle digital media and this content will be opened in the future after those procedures are established and implemented. Please contact the curator of manuscripts at manuscripts@nyhistory.org for further information.
  - Subseries IX.A. Audiocassettes, 1973-1995
    - BJK interview Centre Films, Inc., 1973 November 13 (Offsite-box 52)
      Cassette and accompanying letter from Carol Horton of Centre Films, Inc.
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis promoters meeting (3 cassettes), 1986 December 5 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Curel/ World TeamTennis Radio Revision No Soap, 1995 June 26 (Offsite-box 52)
  - Subseries IX.B. Videocassettes, 1988-2003
    - Domino's Pizza TeamTennis Rec and Pro - 8mm videocassette, 1988 (Offsite-box 52)
    - BJK at Stanford soccer tournament - Mini-DV, 2007 April 28 (Offsite-box 52)
    - BJK at Stanford USTA kids clinic - Mini-DV, 2007 April 28 (Offsite-box 52)
    - World TeamTennis owners meeting - Mini-DV, 2007 November (Offsite-box 52)
    - Hillary Clinton Winter Summit - Mini-DV, 2007 December (Offsite-box 52)
    - ABC News World TeamTennis Elton John and BJK interview - Betacam, circa 1980s (Offsite-box 52)
    - Team Tennis Happy Birthday Billie Jean - VHS, 1993 (Offsite-box 52)
    - World TeamTennis Elton John and BJK - VHS, 1993 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Idols of the Game Babes in Boyland - VHS, 1995 (Offsite-box 52)
      Commercial film produced by Bobkat Productions, Inc. and Turner Original Productions, Inc..
    - Arli$$ Our Past, Our Present, Our Future - VHS, 1999 (Offsite-box 52)
      Season 4 episode 3 of Arli$$ television show, on which BJK was a guest star.
    - Women's Sports Foundation's 23rd Annual Salute to Women in Sports Awards Dinner - VHS, 2002 October 21 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Unforgettable The Little Mo Connolly Story - VHS, 2003 (Offsite-box 52)
      Film by Jennifer Spell.
    - World TeamTennis 2003 sales video approval version - VHS (Offsite-box 52)
    - Dartmouth College commencement - VHS, 2003 (Offsite-box 52)
      Separated Materials
      BJK received honorary doctorate at ceremony.
  - Subseries IX.C. Optical disks [CDs and DVDs], 2001-2018
    - When Billie Beat Bobby - DVD, 2001 (Offsite-box 52)
    - BJK interviews Charles M. Schulz - CD, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52)
      CD copy of 1982 audio from the "Close Encounters" series.
    - Lord & Commons Tennis Club - photo CD, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52)
    - John-Laffnie de Jager Tennis Foundation Tennis for Africa - DVD, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52)
    - One Great Year, a Collection of Gretzky.com Video, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Jim Thompson BJK song and lyrics - CD, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52)
      CD accompanied by typed lyrics to "Billie Jean," music and lyrics by James H. Thompson circa 1975.
    - Freddie Rabuse Homage to BJK - CD, circa 2005 (Offsite-box 52)
      Includes printed lyrics.
    - Crista McAuliffe: Reach for the Stars - DVD, 2006 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Elton John "The Captain and the Kid" - CD, 2006 (Offsite-box 52)
      Signed and inscribed by Elton John to BJK and Ilana Kloss on cover.
    - HealthCorps Gala - DVD, 2007 (Offsite-box 52)
    - HealthCorps Joaquin Perez - DVD, circa 2007 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Screamer Vision Showreels - DVD, 2007 (Offsite-box 52)
      Contains DVD authoring reel and motion graphics reel.
    - WTT Philadelphia Freedoms 2007 Season - photo CD (Offsite-box 52)
    - Human F1RST program video with Patrick Sheahan - DVD, 2008 April (Offsite-box 52)
      Includes inserted handwritten note from Patrick Sheahan to BJK thanking her for her kind remarks played in presenting his portion of the program.
    - Boston University Commencement - DVD, 2008 May 18 (Offsite-box 52)
    - BJK NBC Wimbledon Coverage - DVD (2 disks), 2011 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Pat Engebrecht When Love is Not Enough - CD, 2011 (Offsite-box 52)
    - The Battle of the Sexes - DVD, 2013 (Offsite-box 52)
      Film produced by New Black Films.